Mauricio Borawski

I am a React developer with experience in helping to create and maintain a better code base for reusability. Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills on a larger development team.

Linkedin: /mnborawski Github: /MauricioBorawski

+54 1155776821

mauricio.borawski@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Agrology, Ssr. Front End Developer

August 2023 - Now

Technologies used: React, Typescript, Vitest, Playwright, MUI

- Develop, implement and mantain new features.
- Write integration test and end to end test with a focus on BDD (Behavior Driven Development)
- Create and mantain the style design repo
- Improve code base

Cedeira Software Factory S.R.L, Ssr. Front End Developer

March 2023 - July 2023

Technologies used: React, Typescript, Jest, Redux, MUI

Develop high-quality code with a focus on creating and maintaining comprehensive tests. I work closely with the development team to ensure the delivery of reliable and robust software. Implementing best practices and coding standards ensures our code is scalable, modular, and easily maintainable.

Blockfi, Ssr. React Developer

March 2020 - December 2022

Technologies used: React, Typescript, Jest, Redux, Styled-Components

- Develop new features used by millions of users around the world like introducing ACH and BIA Trading. Increase test coverage from 30% to 98%.
- Write documentation for internal libraries like Goblin.
- Introduce new members of the team to the code base. Explaining to them the code styles and each feature in depth.

SKILLS

React

Git - GitHub

Typescript

Jest - Playwright

StoryBook

Material UI

LANGUAGES

English C2

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

UADE, Software Engineering

March 2023 - Present

Digital House, Full Stack Developer

July 2019-December 2020

- Front End Masters
 JavaScript: The Hard Parts, v2
 Deep JavaScript Foundations, v3